(Howard:)Nothing makes the ladies hotter
than two skinny white guys...
(Howard:)...swatting at each other
with their eyes closed.
(Sheldon:)And unfriend Howard Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)That's all of us. Can I use the laptop?
(Leonard:)- Why?
- I have to buy that stupid collector's tin.
Who do we Iove?
- Penny.
(Penny:)Hello, Sheldon. Come on in.
- Thank you.
- What's up?
(Sheldon:)I came to ask if you would like
to go on a date with me.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, what?
(Sheldon:)A date. You and me.
(Sheldon:)Dining, dancing,
perhaps you'd like to take in a prizefight.
Ugh, God,
are you trying to make Amy jealous?
(Sheldon:)No. Why is everyone so obsessed
with Amy and Stuart?
(Sheldon:)Whether or not they may be having more
pumpkin lattes or intercourse tonight.